esjupiter.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy of Our Email Marketing Service | Emailserving.com EmailServing

## Emailserving, Yesup Ecommerce Solutions Inc. Website and Products Terms and Conditions

### Privacy Policy

#### The Company has agreed to notify you of:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personal identification is collected from you through the web site 
  * The organization collecting the information 
  * How the information is used 
  * With whom the information may be shared 
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under The Company’s control 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information 

### Information Collection and Use

The Company is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The Company collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

#### Information You Upload into Emailserving:

The Company offers self-service direct marketing solutions for small and mid-size businesses. All client data uploaded into our system is stored in a personalized and secure location. The Company will not sell, disclose or rent any client data loaded into our system and only the registered account holder can gain access to the uploaded lists. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our general website. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. Session-based cookies are used by us to determine general effectiveness of marketing campaigns. In such cases, we collect an aggregate number indicating success for that marketing campaign, but do not associate it to any of your personally identifiable information. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our entire site. 

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not associated to personally identifiable information. 

### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with 3rd parties in the case they would like to know aggregate demographics of our audience. This is not associated to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We do not share personally identifiable information with 3rd parties. 

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we the Company are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Emailserving.com. 

### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

This security is reinforced by our use of firewalls protecting all of the Company servers. We also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our customer service representative) are able to access personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every month, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected. Finally, the physical servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure collocation facility, within locked cages that only The Company network administrators have access to. This facility provides security 24 hours a day, 365 days a year and guaranties our servers against power outages by using automated backup power systems. 

### Special Offers

We send all new members a verification email to verify password and username. Established members who have chosen to receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. 

### Administrative Type Email Communications

Please note that we send all new members a verification email to verify password and username. By submitting your email to us when you create an account, your email will be added within our opt-in email contact list. Members will receive periodic emails with information such as newsletters, email promotions on products or services, or special deals, from Emailserving, as well as any companies affiliated with Emailserving as well. If you wish to stop receiving these emails, you can click on the unsubscribe link that’s included with every email or contact us directly.

You will receive administrative emails that are related to the primary usage of our service. You may not opt-out of administrative emails. These administrative emails will not have any marketing, promotional or advertising material(s) in them. 

### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will strive to provide a way to correct and update that user’s personal data provided to us. If you would like your account deactivated please state this in your communications and we will do this. 

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.
